Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 60, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: Your Swift Major Medical Plan for U.S. Salaried Employees and Pensioners, 1967; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: Your Swift Major Medical Plan for U.S. Salaried Employees and Pensioners, 1965; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 11: Your Swift Thrift Plan for U.S. Salaried Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 12: Major Policies and Benefit Plans for U.S. Salaried Employees, 1962; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 13: The Swift Retirement Program, 1961; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 14: Your Swift Hospital Medical Surgical Polio Plan - Statement of Coverage, 1956; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 15: Your Swift Group Life Insurance, 1957; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 16: Major Policies and Benefit Plans for U.S. Salaried Employees, 1962; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 17: Employees Benefit Association Rules and Regulations, 1953; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 18: To All Swift People:, 1952; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 19: Swift & Company Pension Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 20: Your Swift 365-Day Hospital Medical Surgical Polio Plan - Statement of Coverage, 1964; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 21: Your Swift 365-Day Hospital Medical Surgical Polio Plan - Statement of Coverage, 1964; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 22: The Golden Years Series: Covering Many Major Problems of Retirement, 1956; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
    Author: Thomas Collins
  - Item 23: Your Swift Thrift Plan for U.S. Salaried Employees, 1968; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 24: Your Swift Group Life Insurance Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 25: Your Swift Pension Plan for U.S. Employees, 1965; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 26: Major Medical Plan for Salaried Employees and Pensioners, 1963; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 27: Highlights and Rules of Swift & Company Employees Benefit Association, 1964; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 28: Your Swift Thrift Plan for U.S. Salaried Employees, 1962; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
- Box: 60, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Performance Appraisal and Review - A Guide for Effective Use by Management, 1962; Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Your Swift Production Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Wage Chronology No. 7: Swift and Co. - Supplement No. 4, 1955; Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Safety Through Supervision: A Supervisory Development Program, Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Swift & Company's Management: A Training Program for Supervisors, Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Free Correspondence Courses for Swift and Associated Plant Employees, Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Swift's Standard System: A Supervisory Development Program, Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: Employee Relations - A Training Program for Supervisors, Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: How We Live The American Economic System: A Management Training Program, Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: Preventive Maintenance: A Supervisory Development Program, Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 11: Swift & Company's Business: AN Employee Development Program, Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
- Box: 60, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Sylvania Savings and Security Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Sylvania Pension Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Your Group Insurance Benefits, Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Sylvania Savings and Retirement Plan - Rules and Regulations, 1947; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Sylvania Pension Plan for Salary Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Your Group Insurance Benefits, 1965; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 7: Opportunities for College Graduates in the Industrial Relations Trainee Program, Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: They Trained 800 New Workers in a Hurry With Community Help - The Sylvania Story in Batavia, 1954; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 9: Request for Establishment of Salary Classification, 1955; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: Confidential Salary Information Form, Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Box: 60, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 60, Folder 26)
- Box: 61, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: TVA Employees' Safety Guidelines, 1964; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Safety Hints, 1963; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Presentation of National Safety Council President's Medal To Burch Cheek, 1962; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Author: G.O. Wessenauer
  - Item 4: Work Injury Experience, 1965; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Grand Boating But, 1947; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Some Facts on Drownings in TVA Lakes - 1965, 1966; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Office of Power - '64 Safety Report, 1965; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Safety is Part of TVA Plans, Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Author: D.E. Nolting
  - Item 9: Fire Inspections of TVA Properties, Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Vehicular Safety Bulletin, 1966; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Be Fire Safe At Home Too, 1965; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: The President's Conference on Occupational Safety: Safeguarding Human Worth Through Medico-Administrative Skills - IV. Solving Present and Future Problems, 1962; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Author: O.M. Derryberry, M.D., M.P.H.
  - Item 13: Accident Prevention, 1962; Publication (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Box: 61, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Military Policy, 1961; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Employee Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Texaco Today: An International Oil Company in 1972, Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: An International Oil Company in 1967: Texaco Today, Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Texaco Today, Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Opportunities with Texaco, 1967; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Opportunities with Texaco, Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Job Opportunities with The Texas Company, 1954; Publication (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Box: 61, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Military Policy, 1964; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Military Leave Policy: Extended Leaves, 1987; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The New Labor 'Reform' Law - An Appraisal, 1960; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Author: Charles M. Brooks
  - Item 4: New Philosophies in Labor Relations, 1961; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Basic Economics, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The Supervisor And Human Relations, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The Foreman As A Manager, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: What The Employee Has A Right to Expect From His Supervisor, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The Supervisor On The Job, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Report of Interview With the Texas Company, 1950; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Author: Hazel C. Benjamin
  - Item 11: Interview: Mr. E.C. Brehmer, Assistant to the General Manager of Industrial and Public Relations, Texas Company, and more briefly with Mr. James H. Pipkin, General Manager of the Department, and Mr. Avery, his Assistant in charge of Labor Relations, 1951; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Author: Helen Baker
  - Item 12: Air Raid Defense, 1951; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Explanatory Information on Amendments To Group Life Insurance and Pension Plan, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: How to Conduct A Conference, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Letter of Acknowledgement, 1956; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Author: Oscar Lasse
  - Item 16: Stock Ownership, 1956; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Author: W.G. Elicker
  - Item 17: Military Policy, 1958; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Military Policy, 1956; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Accident and Sick Benefit Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: Military Policy, 1955; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: New York Disability Benefits Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: Employment, 1949; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: SRA Verbal Form, 1947; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: Work Sample I: Typing, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: Constitution and By-Laws, 1958; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: Constitution and By-Laws, 1958; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: Military Training and Service Policy, 1948; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Author: Harry T. Klein
  - Item 28: List of Subjects For Which Group Discussion Conference Outlines Have Been Prepared, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 29: Industrial Relations Chart, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 30: Employee's Service Record, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 31: Conference Outline XXIV: Putting Leadership To Work, 1946; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 32: Conference Outline XXV: Building Employee Morale, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 33: Conference Outline XXXI: Induction of New and Transferred Employees, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 34: A Guide To The Veterans' Placement Plan, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 35: Developing and Maintaining Good Communication Channels, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 36: Handling Grievances, Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 37: Accident and Sick Benefit Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 38: Article I: Eligibility to Benefits, 1950; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Item 39: Industrial Relations Organization, 1940; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Author: F.H> Harbison
  - Item 40: Safety Digest: Winners Declared in Competition for The President's Award Trophy and Pipe Liners' Safety Award Plaque, 1956; Publication (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Box: 61, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Texaco Research Center, Publication (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Working in the Shadows, 1958; Publication (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The Labor Relations Outlook - 1959, Publication (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: A Guide for Preparation of Conference Outlines, Publication (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Selection, Training and Development of Service Station Personnel, 1955; Publication (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Beacon Laboratories, Publication (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Box: 61, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Reports of Foremen Conferences, 1924; Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
    Author: L.A. Emerson
  - Item 2: Group Life Insurance and Pension Plan, Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Description of the Group Life Insurance and Pension Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Progress at El Paso, Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Growing With Amrillo: The Story of Amarillo's Refinery, Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Employee Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Employee Benefit Plans, 1954; Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: The Vacation Plan, 1949; Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Description of the Permanent Total Disability Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Employee Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Description of the Hospital and Surgical Benefits Plan for Employees, 1951; Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Labor Policies: Hourly Rated Employees, 1949; Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Let's get Acquainted: A Brief Introduction to The Texas Company, Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Texaco's Heritage; The Way Ahead; Introductory Remarks, 1952; Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
    Author: W.S.S. Rodgers; Harry T. Klein, J.S. Leach
  - Item 15: The Texas Company Presents "Facts", Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Description of the Permanent Total Disability Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Health Division Services, Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: The Training of Saudi Arab Employees: Arabian American Oil Company, 1954; Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 19: Your Visit To Eagle Point Works, Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: You, Your Company and Your Job at Eagle Point Works, Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Item 21: Hospital Surgical Major Medical Benefits Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Box: 61, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: T&P Supervisor and His Job, Publication (Box 61, Folder 6)
    Author: A.L. Kramer, Bass Hoyler, R.A. Downward
- Box: 61, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: TI and You Handbook, 1968; Publication (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Retirement Plan Bulletin, 1970; Publication (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: You Get to Prove How Good You Are in a Technical Career at TI, Publication (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Texas Instruments Incorporated: New Ways to do Things Better in: 1. Research and Development; 2. Materials; 3. Components; 4. Equipments & Systems; 5. Services, Publication (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Box: 61, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Corporate Alumnus Program 1971, 1972; Publication (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Personnel Organization: Leader's Manual, Publication (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Policies and Rules Relating to Appointment Compensation, and Working Conditions of Classified Employees, Publication (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Employees Stock Savings Plan, Publication (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Box: 61, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation of Miscellaneous Union, 1951; Publication (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Welcome to Thatcher, Publication (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Your Group Insurance At Thatcher, 1953; Publication (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Wage Structure Manual - Section 6: Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: All Departments - All Unions; Evaluation Points: Sheet 1 of 2, Publication (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: All Departments - All Unions; Evaluation Points: Sheet 2 of 2, Publication (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Box: 61, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Story of the Thompson Products Old Guard Association, Publication (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Human Relations Policy, 1957; Publication (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: You Are Entering the Service, 1951; Publication (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Box: 61, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Supervisor Induction Program, 1952; Publication (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: A Letter About Your Wage Increase, 1951; Publication (Box 61, Folder 11)
    Author: J.D. Wright
  - Item 3: A Letter About Your Wage Increase, 1951; Publication (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Box: 61, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Cleveland Salary Plan Modified To Reflect Individual Performance, 1961; Publication (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Box: 61, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: 1963 Scholarship Program for Sons and Daughters of Employees of The Timken Roller Bearing Company, Publication (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Safety At Work, At Home, At Play, 1957; Publication (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Box: 61, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Safety Program At The Todd Company, Publication (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Employee Insurance, Publication (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Box: 61, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Tommy Tokheim Plays Safe!, 1948; Publication (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Box: 61, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Information Handbook for Employees of Tompkins County Hospital, Publication (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Box: 61, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Facts About Protection for You and your Family Against Accident and Sickness: Your S.B.A. Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Training & Education, 1957; Publication (Box 61, Folder 18)
    Author: Channing Rice Dooley
  - Item 3: The Labour Scene: Training Within Industry Scheme No Longer Free, 1962; Publication (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Training Within Industry Foundation, 1962; Publication (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Job Economics Training, Publication (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Job Economics Training, 1950; Publication (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Box: 61, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Trane Graduate Training Program, Publication (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Box: 61, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Box: 61, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Cowboys and Engines: The Travelers 1962 Book of Street and Highway Accident Data, Publication (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: Railway Labor Organizations: National Group Insurance Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: What About Major Medical Expenses?, Publication (Box 61, Folder 22)
- Box: 61, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Tremco's Planned Protection for You: Retirement Trust, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Tremco's Planned Protection for You: Annuity (Pension) Plan; Life Insurance; Accident and Sickness Insurance, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: The MST Training Program, 1955; Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: Executive Performance Review, 1952; Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: Terms and Abbreviations, 1952; Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Box: 61, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Performance Appraisal and You: A Handbook for You, 1956; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Box: 61, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Erie Works Apprentice Courses: Developing Young Men for Industrial Careers, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: A Newsletter for Retired Men and Women of GE in Schenectady, 1959; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: The Helping Hand of G-E People, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Employee Turnover In the Schenectady Product Departments, 1954; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: We Gave In Your Name, 1951; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Management Position Guide, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Author: Frank M. Oglee
  - Item 7: Management Development Program, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
- Box: 61, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Are You Missing Something? - Inside Facts About Your Taylor Fellowship Club, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: The Taylor Management Forum: A Management Development Program, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Individual Merit Rating, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
- Box: 61, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Teachers Insurance & Annuity Association College Retirement Equities Fund: CREF - The First Ten Years' Experience, 1962; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Box: 61, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Tennessee Industrial Personnel Conference, 1954; Publication (Box 61, Folder 28)
- Box: 62, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Your Plan for Insurance, Savings and Retirement, 1953; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Box: 62, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Manual - Headquarters Employee Relations Procedure: Non-Exempt Performance Appraisal, 1977; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Career Review Discussion Outline, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Supervisor's Manual - Headquarters Employee Relations Procedure: Employee Opportunity System, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: It's Your Move, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Your Union Carbide Savings Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Union Carbide General Offices, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: Information Sheet
  - Item 7: Layoff Allowance Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: I. Purpose
  - Item 8: Benefit Plans, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Employment of Persons Over Normal Retirement Age, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Retirement Policy, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Our Safety Breakthrough, 1974; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: Back-Grounder: Employee-Community Communications
  - Item 12: A Career At Haynes Stellite for Chemical Engineers, Mechanical Engineers, Metallurgical Engineers, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Annual Safety Report, 1958; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Employment of Persons Over Normal Retirement Age, 1954; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Employment Beyond Normal Retirement Age, 1952; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: The Discovery Company
  - Item 17: Highlights of the Union Carbide Housing Program, 1958; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Union Carbide Scholarships, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: The Union Carbide Educational Fund, 1953; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Notes: News Release from Union Carbide and Carbon Corporation
  - Item 20: Salary Payments During Disability Absence, 1964; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Transfer Kit for Internationally Assigned Employees, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Box: 62, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Equal Employment Opportunity, 1975; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Equal Employment Opportunity, 1976; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: National Carbon Company offers Positions with Potential, Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Information for UCC Employees in the New York Metropolitan Area, 1954; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Information for Employees in the New York General Offices, Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: About You and Your Job at Bakelite, 1951; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The Stellite Story, 1952; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: You at Prest-O-Lite, 1953; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: You and Your Job at Electromet, 1953; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Savings Plan for Employees, 1953; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Savings Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Savings Plan for Employees, 1960; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Savings Plan for Employees, 1957; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Welcome to Union Carbide Plastics Company, Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Box: 62, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan for California Employees, 1954; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The Retirement Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Pension Plan, 1973; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Your Union Carbide Pension Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: You Union Carbide Retirement Program, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)